<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Tetetete</title>
        <link>https://Tete-Tete.github.io/post/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Tetetete</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>Tetetete</copyright><atom:link href="https://Tete-Tete.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>MyFirstBlog</title>
        <link>https://Tete-Tete.github.io/p/myfirstblog/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://Tete-Tete.github.io/p/myfirstblog/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Resume</title>
        <link>https://Tete-Tete.github.io/p/resume/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://Tete-Tete.github.io/p/resume/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yate Zhang&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;mailto:Yatezhang123@gmail.com&#34; &gt;Yatezhang123@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;, 850-533-2734, 211 E. Delaware, Apt 804, Chicago, IL 60611&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDUCATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The University at Buffalo&lt;/strong&gt;                   							                     Buffalo, NY                                                                          &lt;em&gt;Bachelor of Arts in &lt;strong&gt;Statistics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;                                                                    May 2024&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cumulative GPA&lt;/strong&gt;: 3.67/4.0 &lt;strong&gt;|&lt;/strong&gt; Dean’s List Fall 2022&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relevant Coursework:&lt;/strong&gt; Statistical Methods, Intro Stat Inference, Distribution Free Inference, Intro to Probability, Linear Algebra, Calculus, Systems Programming, Data Structures, Discrete Structures, Computer Science&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Northwestern University&lt;/strong&gt;                                                                    Chicago, IL&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Master of School of Professional Study in&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Science&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;                                     Expected: August 2025&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;	&lt;/code&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relevant Coursework:&lt;/strong&gt; Computer Science, Machine Learning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ipsos, Healthcare Group&lt;/strong&gt;                                                                 Shanghai, China&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Data Analyst Intern&lt;/em&gt;							          	    				             06/2023-08/2023&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participated in a market research project for a pulmonary arterial hypertension (PAH) product of a  pharmaceutical company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designed an interview questionnaire and conducted phone interviews to collect information on medication details of patients with PAH as well as key influencing factors in the decision-making process of purchasing medication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cleaned and organized interview data, debugged the data storage website using Python, and conducted PAH treatment competitive analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyzed and identified key indicators and proposed marketing and brand strategies for sale force performance and marketing activity of the new PAH product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Software Engineering Center Chinese Academy of Sciences&lt;/strong&gt;          	                        Beijing, China&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Data Analyst Intern&lt;/em&gt;       							          	    					 12/2022-01/2023&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collected relevant project information from local governments and cleaned and standardized the gathered data, which included supplementing information on the contracting units and project leaders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independently calculated data indicators, queried old data in the database using SQL, and updated new data into the database with ETL tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisted in optimizing project data prediction model algorithms with Python, and recorded model results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PROJECT EXPERIENCE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instant Messenger&lt;/strong&gt;                             				                         04/2022-05/2022&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Studied the given instant messaging protocol and determined the data packet format&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performed packet encoding and decoding for the protocol in C by utilizing functions from the string.h library&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applied GDB and run tests to check and identify potential issues during the encoding and decoding processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Priority Queue&lt;/strong&gt;                                                                         03/2022-04/2022&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implemented the linked list with pointers and structures in C&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wrote complete and sophisticated unit tests to verify core functionality and detect possible errors, and learned to validate the integrity of a data structure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;League of Legends Esports, Buffalo University&lt;/strong&gt;                               					 Buffalo, NY&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Game player and Team Data Analyst&lt;/em&gt;                                    				      09/2022-05/2024&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collected and organized over 100 sets of game data and used Python to analyze key performance indicators such as KDA (kill/death/assist ratio), champion win rates, and overall win rates, to track individual and team performances&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conducted analyses on opponents’ game data to gather insights into their strategies, and proposed recommendations for gameplay tactics accordingly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presented game statistics in written reports and participated as a Support Player in training sessions and matches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SKILLS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Computer skills&lt;/strong&gt;: C, Java, Python, SQL, Scala, Excel, Minitab, Coq&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language&lt;/strong&gt;: Fluent in Chinese and proficient in English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Self-introduction</title>
        <link>https://Tete-Tete.github.io/p/test-chinese/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://Tete-Tete.github.io/p/test-chinese/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About me
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;My name is Yate Zhang. I am Chinese and moved to the USA when I was 14 years old. I completed my high school education in Pensacola, Florida, and earned my undergraduate degree in Statistics from SUNY Buffalo. Initially, I pursued Computer Science during my freshman year but switched to Statistics in my sophomore year as I found Computer Science to be quite challenging. I am currently studying Data Science at Northwestern University. While it may sound daunting, I am dedicated to improving my coding skills and doing my best in this field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;graph&#34;&gt;Graph
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://Tete-Tete.github.io/p/test-chinese/coding.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;1024&#34;
	height=&#34;1024&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://Tete-Tete.github.io/p/test-chinese/coding_hu7121050639221747846.jpg 480w, https://Tete-Tete.github.io/p/test-chinese/coding_hu13804562557099960442.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Photo by ChatGPT&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;100&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;240px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
